INFO

Residence

Morocco, Berrechid

Nationality

Morocco

Birthdate

1998/10/14

Gender

Male

Phone

abdo.zad.raja2@gmail.com

Email

+212680096104

Website

www.zadelkhair.me

SKILLS

BACKEND

LARAVEL
PHP
REST API
SQL
GRAPH QL
JAVA

FRONTEND

VUFJS ANGULAR JS REACT NATIVE 00000 HTML 00000 **CSS** 00000 JS 00000 **BOOTSTRAP JQUERY VUFX** 00000

DATABASE

MYSQL
SQL SERVER
ORACLE DB
SQL LITE
FIREBASE

MODELING

UML •••••
MERISE

ZADELKHAIR ABDELKODDOUS

Full stack web developer

PROFILE

My name is ABDELKODDOUS ZADELKHAIR I'm 23 years old, full stack web developer (LARAVEL & VUEJS) with a vast array of knowledge in many different front end and back end languages, responsive frameworks, databases, desktop and mobile applications (C# and JAVA). and best coding practices.

EDUCATION

2020 - 2021 Bachlor Of Computer Science
 University Ibn Zohr, Taroudant
 i got my bachelor of computer science with
 honor degree (16/20).
 2018 - 2020 Skilled Technician in Software Development
 Diploma
 ISTICG OFPPT, Berrechid
 I got this diploma in software development with
 honor degree (17/20).
 2016 - 2017 Height School Diploma
 Ouled Hriz, Berrechid

high school diploma scientific Ouled Hriz Berrechid.

EXPERIENCE

2021 - Present stock management system

direction des impôts, Marrakech

Stock management application for the human resources department of the tax administration in Marrakech.

2021 - Present elwadifa.info

freelance job announcement website.

2021 - 3 traineeship at AGRI4.0

months Agri 4.0, AGADIR

3-month internship at the agri 4.0 company, I developed during this internship a mobile application that manages a nursery with reactnative laravel technology.

2020 - 5 Frontend developer at ZadTech

months ZadTech, Elmohammadia

Frontend developer (vuejs and angular) at

zadtech company.

DISKTOP 2016-2020 IT administrator at Al-Khayrat C# Al-khayrat, Berrechid i worked as an it administrator, i have .NET developed during this period multiple **JAVA** 00000 application, Candidate administration desktop application with c#), code permis al **MOBILE** khayrat (android version with java , disktop **JAVA** application with c#, web version with php **ANDROID** laravel'/vuejs) **REACT NATIVE** 2021 utory.ma **FIREBASE** freelance, Berrechid UTORY, school management course online **OTHER** With laravel and vuejsWith laravel and vuejs. npm 00000 git 2019-2021 Fullstack web developer Freelancer ubuntu 20 Morocco Fullstack web developer laravel/vuejs windows server 00000 webpack 00000 2021 Code permis access 0000 Alkhavrat. Berrechid Code permis, android application with Java excel and SQLite word 0000 powerpoint 00000 2020 **Code Alkhayrat** Alkhavrat. Berrechid **DESIGN** CODE AL KHAYRAT, with laravel/vuejs and Design Software graphql Photoshop 2020 **Dental care** illustrator Frelance, Berrechid adobe xd dental care Web application with LARAVEL figma and VUEJS **ISTICG** 2019 ISTICG. Berrechid timeline table desktop management,

application with c# and sql server